Guide to the Records of the Office of External Affairs, Commencement and Special Events RG.7.4
New York University Archives
- Series I: Events
  - Alumni Relations: NYU Picnic (1/2), Sep 14, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Relations: NYU Picnic (2/2), Sep 14, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Alumni Relations Weekend, Jun 1991 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058072 5
  - Dental School 125th: PH Dinner, May 22, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Ireland House, May 20, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Charles Haughey, PM of Ireland, May 1991 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Council Meeting and Dinner, May 8, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Council: Awards Comm., May 1991 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Green Thumb '91, Apr 23, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Hub N Apple Concert II, Apr 13, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Dean Oppenheim Farewell, Apr 11, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Distinguished Alumni, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Office of Sponsored Programs, Feb 26, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Entertainment: Albany Day, Feb 26, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - NYU in Albany Day (1/3), Feb 26, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - NYU in Albany Day (2/3), Feb 26, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - NYU in Albany Day (3/3), Feb 26, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Homecoming: Basketball, Feb 17, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058071 7
  - Alumni Relations: Homecoming, Feb 17, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Alumni: Florida Gathering, Jan 19, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Second Annual NYU Picnic, Oct 3, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - 1992 Alumni Council Dinner, Jun 1, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Mayor Sobchak Visit, May 1, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Washington Square Park Tragedy, Apr 23, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Village Improvement Day, Apr 21, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Windows Project, Spring 1992 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Andreotti Book Reception, Mar 10, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - NYU in Albany (1/2), Feb 25, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - NYU in Albany (2/2), Feb 25, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - All University Dinner Dance, Oct 22, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - 1992 Conference: "De Benedetti" Visit, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - 1992 NYU Conference, Apr 1992 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058070 9
  - Bobst Awards Dinner, Dec 4, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Havel Information, Oct 27, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Havel Guest List, Oct 27, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Havel Convocation, Oct 27, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Federation Dinner, Oct 23, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Classroom Dedication (1/2), Sep 21, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Classroom Dedication (2/2), Sep 21, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Borris Yeltsin Address, Jun 21, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Ireland House Dedication (1/3), Apr 26, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058069 1
  - Ireland House Dedication (2/3), Apr 26, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Ireland House Dedication (3/3), Apr 26, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Stern M.E.C. Dedication, Apr 23, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Park Accident: 1st Anniversary, Apr 23, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - International Rectors' Conference, Apr 1993 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - 1992-93 Regional Basketball Game Receptions, Jan 13, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Triangle Shirtwaist Fire Plaque, Mar 25, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - NYU in Albany, Feb 23, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - NYU in Albany Day, Feb 23, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058068 3
  - Prime Minister Reynolds Visit, Sep 15, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Council Meeting, Jan 28, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Washington Square News, Winter 1992 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Macy's Thanksgiving Day Parade, Nov 26, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Federation Finance Forum, Nov 14, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Varsity Club Awards Dinner, Oct 28, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Italian / American Heritage Month Celeb., Oct 15, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Federation Awards Dinner, Oct 15, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Stern / Coles Volleyball Night, Oct 14, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Hopkins-Pechar Golf and Tennis, Oct 13, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - New Jersey Alumni Clubs Dinner, Oct 8, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Social Work / Foundling Event, Apr 25, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058067 5
  - NYU in Albany, Feb 23, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - SSW and Founding Hospital, Apr 25, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Albany Day, Mar 1, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Albany Day, Mar 1, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Science and Math Ed. Conference, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend 1995, Jun 1995 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Council Meetings, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Student Senators Dinner, Feb 2, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Chet Huntley Book Party, Dec 10, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - 9th Annual Albany Day, Mar 1, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - 1994 Gallatin Lecture: Shimon Peres, Sep 29, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - SSW Dedication, Sep 19, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Cuomo / C.A.T. Reception, Mar 21, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - H.E.O.P. - 25th Anniversary, Apr 29, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Heights Centennial, Apr 17, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Federation Political Forum, May 4, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - V.I.P. Day, Apr 27, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Federation Finance Forum, Nov 19, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Musical Theatre Hall of Fame, Nov 16, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - President Eanes Visit, Sep 18, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Tolbert's Convocation, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - President Karamanlis Visit, Apr 6, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Varsity Club Dinner, Oct 20, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Fed: Varsity Club Dinner, Oct 20, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Alumni Federation Awards Dinner, Oct 13, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Alumni Council Meeting, Oct 11, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Silverstein Lounge Dedication, Apr 21, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - NYU Picnic, Sep 7, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Social Work Dedication, Sep 19, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Brown Plus Forty, Apr 13, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058066 7
  - Shimkin Classrooms Naming, Apr 5, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - CAT/ Cuomo Reception, Mar 24, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - NYS Commission on National and Community Service, Mar 21, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Heyman Hall, Mar 14, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - NYU in Albany Day, Mar 1, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - 1994 "NYU in Florida", Feb 16, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Regional UAA Basketball Receptions, Dec 5, 1993-Feb 20, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Federation Finance Forum, Nov 20, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Seventh Annual All University Dinner Dance, Nov 4, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Varsity Club Awards Dinner, Oct 28, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Tax Society and Money Marketeers, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Finance and Business Club, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Westchester / Fairchild Counties Reception, Oct 6, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - 1994 Gallatin Lecture: S. Peres, Sep 29, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Shimon Peres Visit, Sep 28, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Main Building Lounges and Lecture Hall, Fall 1993 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Annual NYU Alumni Cruise, Jun 6, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, Jun 1993 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Council Dinner, Jun 1, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Honorary Degree Convocation, Jun 10, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Acceptance lists for Convocation and Reception, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Academic Convocation: Kim Young Sam, Oct 23, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058065 9
  - Kim Convocation: Marching Letters, Oct 23, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Kim Convocation: General Invite, Oct 23, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Kim Convocation: Information Desk, Oct 23, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - President Kim Visit, Oct 23, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Kim Young Sam Visit: General, Oct 23, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Gallatin Convocation: Marching Letters, Oct 12, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Gallatin Convocation, Oct 12, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Federation of New York University, Inc., 1989 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058064 2
  - Meritorious Service Awards Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Directors Emeriti Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Tax on Gifts, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Service Corporation, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Meritorious Service Awards Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Meritorious Service Awards Recommendations, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Federation of New York University, Inc., 1989 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Federation Nominating Committee, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Nominating Committee of the Alumni Federation, Mar 30, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Nominating Committee Meeting, Apr 1, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Prof. Alumni Assoc., 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Director of Emeritus Award Past Recipients, 1976-1991 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - The Federation Annual Dinner, May 24, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Great Teachers, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Meritorious Service Awards Recommendations, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Meritorious Service Awards Committee Meeting, Apr 16, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Meritorious Service Awards Committee, Apr 17, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Meritorious Service Awards Committee, Apr 12, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Meritorious Service Awards, Apr 12, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Meritorious Service Award, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Meritorious Formula Sub-Committee Combinations, 1967-1978 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Budget, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Budget, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Budget, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058063 4
  - Finance Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Finance Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Health, Welfare and Benefit Fund Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - NYU Alumni Federation Health, Welfare & Benefits Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Health, Welfare, & Benefit Fund Committee Meeting, Jun 7, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Health, Welfare, & Benefit Fund Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Health, Welfare, & Benefit Fund Committee, 1976-1979 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Board Plans and Board Meeting, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Health, Welfare, & Benefit Fund, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Finance Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Alumni Counts by School, 1982-1985 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Federation Student Relations Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Travel Committee (Federation Committee), 1985 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Special Services Committee, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Federation: Committee on Relations with the University, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Black Book Originals, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Health, Welfare, and Benefit Fund Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Allocation Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Health, Welfare, and Benefit Fund, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend: Memorabilia, Jun 1995 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058062 6
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend: Envelopes, Jun 1995 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - NYU Magazine, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058061 8
  - The Friends of LaGuardia Place, Oct 19, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Albert Gallatin Lecture: Shimon Perez (1/2), Sep 29, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - University: New York University in New York City, Winter 1992 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Report on Graduate Education in America Pub., 1984 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Named Professorships, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058060 0
  - NYU / Night, undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - The USA Up Close by Giulo Andreotti, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - School of Social Work Dedication, Sep 19, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Instructions for attaching NYU emblems, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - International Dimensions at NYU, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - NYU calendar, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Alma Mater, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Mitterand Convocation, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Ireland House Dedication, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Kim Convocation, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Gallatin Convocation, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - All-University Orientation Guide, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - NYU Celebrates 2000 Promotional Material, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - NYU Celebrates 2000 Instructions and Script, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - NYU Celebrates 2000 Photos, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Welcome Day, 2016 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Inauguration, Hamilton (1 of 2), 2016 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Inauguration, Hamilton (2 of 2), 2016 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Honors/Awards Events, 2014, 2016 (Box 43, Folder 1, 3-4)
  - A Celebration of the Life of Nancy Murphy Cricco, 2015 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Series II: Publications
  - Milton Petrie Lecture, Feb 26, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058059 2
  - Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies, Mar 1987 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Spring Celebration, Apr 4, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Leonard Stern Hall Dedication, May 1987 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - NYU Alumni Cruise, Sep 18, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Special Convocation: David Kriser Central Center, Nov 18, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - All Libraries Convocation Samples, Dec 15, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Milton Petrie Lecture In Entrepreneurship, Mar 10, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Second Annual Spring Celebration, Apr 20, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Special Academic Convocation: Francois Mitterand, Sep 20, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Special Academic Celebration: Alexander Onassis, Oct 10, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058058 4
  - Third Annual All-University Dinner Dance, Nov 8, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - All-University Dinner Dance, Oct 20, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Alexander Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies, Nov 13, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - NYU Calendar Book, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Night, Nov 15, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - The Time Award: Corazon Aquino, Sep 18, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Academic Convocation: Dr. Alfred Gottschalk, Oct 28, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Courant 50th Anniversary, Oct 22, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058057 6
  - Shimon Peres Convocation, Oct 21, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 2, Box Shared University Archives 002)
  - Alfonsin Convocation, Mar 21, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Winter Celebration, Mar 2, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Iakovos Convocation, Nov 25, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Third Annual Faculty Convocation, Nov 14, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - All-University Dinner Dance, Oct 22, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Andreotti Special Convocation, Mar 8, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - 33 Third Avenue Brochure, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - NYU in Albany Day, Feb 27, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058056 8
  - Rita Sussmuth "The Future of Europe", Mar 19, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Kaifu Special Convocation, Sep 28, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Salinas Special Convocation, Oct 1, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Kim Convocation - Programs, Oct 23, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Kim Convocation, Oct 23, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Prime Minister Albert Reynolds' Luncheon, Sep 15, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058055 0
  - Alumni in Florida, Jan 19, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Founders Day, Apr 18, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Founders Day, Apr 8, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Founders Day, Apr 26, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Founders Day, Apr 21, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Founders Day, Apr 22, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Founders Day, Apr 16, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Founders Day, Apr 24, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Founders Day, Apr 23, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058054 3
  - Annual Report, 1977-1984 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - New York University Development Campaign, Sep 1985-Aug 1988 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - NYU Magazine, 1990-1991 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - NYU Magazine, 1989-1990 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - NYU Magazine, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - NYU Magazine, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - AmeriCorps: Project Safety Net, Fall 1984 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Gala Dinner Dance, Nov 3, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058053 5
  - Invitations for Convocation for Jehan El-Sadat, Mar 25, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Runciman Convocation, Oct 18, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Fourth Annual Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture, Nov 10, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - King of Spain Dinner R.S.V.P., Dec 6, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - King of Spain Convocatoin, Nov 2, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Bobst 10th Anniversary, Oct 25, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Convocation, Oct 11, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - 1982 Calendar (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Student Handbook, 1979-1984 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058052 7
  - NYU 150th Anniversary, Oct 13, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Mayor's Proclamation (Sesquicentennial), Oct 13, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Night, Mar 22, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Havel Convocation, Oct 27, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Gallatin Convocation, Oct 12, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Classroom Dedication, Sep 20, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Casa Italiana Zerilli-Marimo Dedication, Nov 13, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058051 9
  - All University Dinner Dance, Oct 22, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - All University Dinner Dance, Nov 7, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Ireland House Dedication, Apr 26, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Annual Picnic Sample Info, Oct 2, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Founders Day, Apr 18, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Founders Day, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Founders Day Program, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - Founders Day Programs, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - Ireland House Dedication Programs, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Gallatin Convocation Program, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 40)
- Series III: Commencement
  - Commencement Message to Students in Service, 1918 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Address, 1918 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Addresses, 1923-1929 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Addresses, 1930, 1933-1939 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Program, 1930 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Program, 1934 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Program, 1938 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Commencement Program, 1939 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Commencement Addresses, 1940-1942 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Commencement Program, 1940 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Commencement Program, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Commencement Program, 1942 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1943 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Commencement Program, 1944 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1945 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1946 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Commencement Program, 1946 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Commencement Addresses, 1947-1949 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Commencement Programs, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Commencement Program, 1948 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Commencement Program, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Commencement Programs, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Commencement Programs, 1951 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Commencement Program, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Commencement Programs, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Commencement Programs, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1954 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Commencement Programs, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Commencement Programs, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1957 (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - Commencement Programs, 1957 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - Commencement Program, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - Commencement Programs, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 45)
  - Commencement Programs, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 46)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 47)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Programs, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Programs, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Programs, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Commencement Programs, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Commencement Programs, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Commencement Programs, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Commencement Programs, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Commencement Programs, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Commencement Programs, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Commencement Planning, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Commencement Program, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Baccalaureate Ceremony, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Commencement Program, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Commencement Program, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Commencement Planning, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Commencement Planning, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Commencement Programs, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Commencement Programs, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Commencement Programs, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 38)